Finding Aid for the Nancy A. Ransom Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Nancy A. Ransom Papers
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0361
3.35 linear feet
- Book Reviews by Nancy Ransom (Box 1)
- Vanderbilt Commencement Announcement 12 May 1989 (Box 1)
- “The National Planning Board” by Nancy Anne Alderman ’50 (Jan. 1950) (Box 1)
- Newspaper clippings about Ransom—1980’s (Box 1)
- Newspaper clippings about Ransom—1970’s – 80’s (Box 1)
- Nancy’s Doctoral Dissertation, Copyright Registration and Dedication (Kinko’s box) (Box 2)
- Lecture notes, syllabi for Soc./WS 250 Spring ‘91 (Box 2)
- Athena Award 1992—Correspondence, congratulations, nominations (Box 2)
- Stress Management Workshop—Handouts ‘92 (Box 2)
- Leadership America Luncheon—Welcome June 28, 1993 (Box 2)
- B + PW Talk: “Many-faceted women,” May 27, 1993 and correspondence (Box 2)
- College of Charleston; Women’s Studies Consultation—Oct. 1, 2, 1993 (Box 2)
- Stress Management Booklets ’94 –‘96 (Box 3)
- American Association for Adult and Continuing Education: Dinner Speech, 11/02/94 (Box 3)
- Stress Management Workshop (Medical Receptionists); April 5, 1995 (Box 3)
- Southern Festival of Books ’96; Panel: Braden, Walker, Ransom (Box 3)
- Common Sense Stress Management for Women, October 16, 1996 (Box 3)
- MTSU Women’s Leadership Conference—March 7, 1997 (Box 3)
- Handouts: Family and Work (Box 3)
- Handouts: Body Image and Self-Esteem (Box 3)
- Paper: “Self-Image among Undergraduate Women...” Lodge Study. First paper (Box 3)
- Paper: “Self-Image Among Undergraduate Women...” SEWSA Conference 1993 – final (Box 3)
- Lectures, speeches: 1980 – 1992 (Box 3)
- Vassar 50th Reunion presentation—June 2000 (Box 3)
- Photo Album—China Trip (Box 4)
- Russia Trip—Postcards (Box 4)
- China Trip—Women’s music (Box 4)
- China Trip—Postcards (Box 4)
- China Trip—Slides 1 (Box 5)
- China Trip—Slides 2 (Box 5)
- Leadership Manual - “People to People” - for Citizen Ambassador Program Delegation Leaders (Box 5)
- “People to People” folder: itinerary, flight information, delegates list (Box 5)
- U. S. Women and Sport—Women in Society Delegation—China Trip (Box 5)
- China Trip—information; journals, notes, etc. -Ginling College info. (Box 5)